Welcome to Manulife Vitality Stories!
Once upon a time, Matthew wondered, “How do I use the Manulife Vitality app?”
So he opened up to Chapter 1.
First, he needed to download the app.
It’s simple! He just went to the App Store or Google Play and found the one called “Manulife Vitality”.
Now that he had the app, in Chapter 2 it was time to try it out!
The first thing he saw was the home screen – where everything he needed was at his fingertips!
He could see his status level, number of points, navigation buttons along the bottom, some posts, his Weekly Target progress and more.
Clicking “Profile” opened up a new right navigation to access more features, including settings.
Matthew couldn’t wait to earn Vitality Points – and Chapter 3 shows the app was just bursting with ways to earn them.
Check these out!
Now let’s take a quick look at how Matthew completed his Vitality Health Review.
He clicked “Activities,” then “Reviews” and “Vitality Health Review.”
From there, he clicked “Start review” and answered some questions on his way to earning a quick 500 points!
Everything in the app was cool, but the most fun part had to be collecting rewards. So it’s time for Chapter 4.
When Matthew reached his weekly activity goal, he earned a Vitality Spin and was notified on the home screen.
He clicked “Rewards,” clicked to spin, then swiped to spin the wheel to automatically win gift cards or points!
He answered the easy math question and, BOOM, he was a winner!
If he won a gift card, he would click the big pink button at the top of the Rewards screen to collect his digital gift card, with a code and PIN that he could use right away.
And we close with Chapter 5, as Matthew knew that with all the points and rewards he could collect through the app, he’d live happily ever after!
Want to check out more Manulife Vitality “how-to” stories?
Click on one of the other videos you see here, then you could live happily ever after!